# Hey there! I'm Pedro, a Product Designer based in Málaga

# Currently

I'm working as a Senior Product Designer at Verisk - specialty business solutions, a SAAS product provider for Insurance services. We're working on many different projects, from improving the user experience to creating new business opportunities. My responsibilities as Design Manager are setting up the Design department tasks over its Backlog and Sprints, working in MVPs from early stages, defining workflows in and out the Design department, unifying the experienes across all products, meeting with stakeholders, work in analysis and prototyping stages, auditing Accessibility, creating internal initiatives...

# Daily Work

Usability Accesibility

Prototypes Wireframes

Interaction Research

UI Code

## Experience

#### Senior Product Designer

Verisk (Feb 2020 - now)

#### Senior Product Designer

Ravenpack (Apr 2018 - Feb 2020)

Researching to build new features, low and high fidelity wireframing and rapid prototyping for validation. Assisting Developers in implementation. And iterate.

#### **Product Designer**

Basebone (Mar 2017 - Apr 2018)

Building a new family of digital products from scratch using a mobile first mindset. Researching, wireframing, prototyping and assisting Developers.

#### **CRO** Designer

Basebone (Mar 2015 - Mar 2017)

Designing and coding websites for Conversion Rate Optimization in the Marketing Affiliation industry.

### Web Designer

Freelance (Mar 2013 - Apr 2015)

During this stage I created my own multimedia agency, in which I worked for so many different projects having different responsabilities, like Graphic Design, Web Design and Developing, Video Director and Editor.

## Designer and Web Developer

Dantex Group (Mar 2012 - Apr 2013)

Designing and coding web projects using Actionscript 3.0 (Flash) and HTML5 environments, for clients like Deloitte, BNP Parisbas, Prosegur or HA Barceló.

## Audiovisual experience

Various (Sep 2007 - Mar 2012)

I worked as Video Director and Editor, Motion Grapher in several agencies and broadcasting media, such as TVE, Cuatro, Teatros del Canal and SATSE.

## Education

Universidad de Salamanca

Ingeniería Técnica en Informática de Sistemas

2005

Licenciatura en Comuniación Audiovisual

2007

Luma Institute

Design Thinking Essentials 2021

Torres Burriel

Usabilidad y Experiencia de Usuario 2017

CICE

Máster en Desarrollo de Aplicaciones Actionscript 3.0 , con Joseba Alonso 2011